[Music]
when they come
and they will i'll come for you
i have an army we have a hulk oh i
thought the beast had wandered off
you're missing the point there's no
throne there is no version of this
where you come out on top let me
infiltrate the beat
concentrate the heat if you ain't on my
level
[__] it let me be i'll be going till
it's all in motion talking killing
rappers then i hit my quarter and my
train of thought is more a locomotive
talking reason for it
all right guys i am [__] dirty from
that flight
it's actually a decent place it's all i
kind of need is a bed in here
only going to be here for a few days i
have a date
so i got to shower up that's the shower
looks like a shower in there
and and then going street is just packed
full of people it's like a party here
all the time
people in the hallways downstairs you
know
it's freaking cool here
[Music]
now boys my experience so far with miami
is it has nothing it's nothing compared
to uh
to vancouver vancouver's so so much
better because it's kind of
it's got like all this nature and hikes
and mountains
um and the weather is not just like
blistering hot where you have to like
sit down you know what i mean
and and here it's such a vibe
to party right and to uh you know have
drinks and
chill at the beach and stuff like that
and just basically get nothing done
in your life um so vancouver is a much
more productive
healthier city that's my experience this
is a great vacation spot it kind of
makes me think of
like a mixture between like it's like
cancun during the day
and then i guess at night minus the
gambling
and that's very much the vibe here um so
i have been taking
a little bit of a break off of my uh
health binge
uh and i've been having a few drinks and
been eating
unhealthy uh but we're on vacation for a
few days and then we're gonna go right
back to it once we get back in town
and we're gonna do that that webinar um
and
so hopefully by that i guess by the time
you guys see this it's probably already
gonna be running but that webinar is
gonna be really really good we're gonna
really focus on trading get tons of
trading done teach a few people
because this is the only chance
somebody's actually going to be able to
be mentored for me forever
because i'm done i'm done teaching no
more i'm too good at trading now i don't
want to teach you guys and that's about
it
right boys we landed in
columbus here meeting up with the k
valor
to do some uh some videos together
after the miami trip and so just a quick
stop on the way home
it's actually super cold on the east
coast i didn't realize hopefully i can
get cleaned up or something at his place
when i get there
hopefully he's got a shower because i
thought um
i'm not at fort lauderdale it was a
small airport
this is this like looks like a bus
station it's like
it's like one room and there's like well
i guess maybe two
two three plane gates is a really small
airport
we've been on you know a health trip
right lately doing everything for
happiness
productivity proper health and
everything right
and uh miami just freaking blew it out
of the water
and we took a break from it
and we went to strip clubs and i dropped
at least 10 grand in the past five days
in miami we got to figure out how i want
to get home still but we're going to be
right back to the
right back to the health and everything
once we get back home here we took a
break from it for a little bit but it
was not too bad
but miami's just it's just a [__]
terrible place
it was fun though it was fun my [__]
hair is haggard that's him man
let's jump in dude check out this new uh
filter
find a camera fire yo yo yo it's a boy
yeah so valor here is uh he's an ict
trader he's been uh trading for five
years now only recently kind of uh
killing it so he's branching out other
investments i was talking to him a
little bit in the car here on the ride
so i think
we might watch like some ict type stuff
talk talk a lot
about more that style trading because i
think we're kind of similar
uh traders uh in in that style uh and
then
a couple videos on you know but yeah the
reaction stuff like a little q a because
some people ask me some questions
[Music]
all right guys i think that's all we're
doing um for the
day here we recorded a few videos of
reaction there a couple things
we're gonna go grab some chicken because
we missed out on chicken this morning
uh and then we'll be rocking out
perfectly these boggle roosters ready
roosters i'm pretty sure roosters is a
strip club in canada
bro
traveling's overrated
and the final
challenge of the trip here boys is
uh looks like
we got to take a car ride here i still
don't have a kova test
to get home this is dark hopefully they
let me across the border
i know on the passport it says that they
can't deny me um so i'm just going based
off that i know you're supposed to have
a covetous to get in
uh mine is like five days old so don't
think they're gonna allow it
total of 38 hours assuming i
can get across the border 30 hours stay
across home
i have this car for 24 hours super
expensive 400 bucks man
i think that trip cost me about 10 grand
you guys are probably wondering how the
[__] hunter hunter how the [__]
did you spend 10 grand in miami in what
four or five days well
a bunch of flights i had to fly to ohio
too there there's eight flights in total
i got this rent-a-car i bought the
laptop
uh and the biggest expense boys uh miami
has strip clubs
and uh let's fix that and i went twice
uh and uh uh when i got a strip club man
i didn't take this lightly because it's
been a long time since i've been out
so i there was like about six grand
throne
not not thrown but we went to the back
rooms that was about it so the trip
itself if you don't count like the
strippers was about
was about four grand uh the laptop and
everything two grand
so they're actually like flying and
flying into combinations was like two
three grand something like that
but i spent well over 10 grand for sure
just actually
might be invited to a friend's house
tonight
uh we'll go chat with her but uh tell
her some stories
uh but we're not gonna we're not gonna
record that part
so funny so after all this um
my friend was wrong you still have to
stay in the hotel
if you drive over the border i just want
to go home now uh
so they're gonna find me with two they
said
they're gonna find me with a hotel
there's like two grand
and then another 3 400 for not doing the
[__] covid test
oh good thing 1500 trip for five days
guys i'm back it's been a while back and
i've just basically been
chilling at home um not doing much let's
fix this focus
auto focus boom easy peasy look what the
[__]
the cast just did though i'm in the
middle of
um streaming doing a uh an actual
live stream right now and i see them
[__] destroying [__] here
uh miami was great but it took me a
whole [__] week of just
recovering sleeping um and now we're
back on this uh this grind here
and uh came back to the normal life i
gotta clean this [__] up see you guys
later all right what's up traders 100fx
i'm going to show you
how we locked in just about 10 r
in the week here uh trading just the
euro dollar i'm trading all the time
frames
and i did this all on live stream for
you guys so if you guys did want to join
in on that live stream there's a link in
the description
hunter fx dot co slash live
um and then you guys can follow the live
streams as well
um and uh we're just gonna show you some
of the clips here uh but i'm also gonna
show you
uh kind of the trades that i did take
here i did take a log of the trades here
let me just pull them up
yeah so this uh this week here we
actually only traded
um we actually only traded three of the
days because there was that holiday on
the us there so if we look
at the trades let's pull these up here
and i'm gonna show you some clips of
this actually live uh so this was the
first day
uh we took a short into the uh the
london session here
after it was really just dropping off
really really hard uh we
we quickly looked for kind of a retest
after we saw this consolidation we
entered on that retest stop above the
range here and then just continue down
we took two and a half r on that one but
this is this is showing good signs for
the bulls here right so we wouldn't want
to get in yet
there's another possibility of what
happens here it comes up here
re-test that zone and then jumps down
and then that would give us
exactly what we're looking for actually
because we want to test this area
the range would be
the range would be like roughly like
something like this right
and this one this would be rough
roughly the range yeah uh so this makes
more sense here
um we had a really big wick here
actually
um this would make more sense because
then we would go for just exactly where
we're targeting
just sweep these lows as well that'd
probably be what's going to happen here
right uh i mind you this would be this
would be super fine too
because this is the the five minute
breaker right
so i'd be happy with shorting this here
if we if we break back down below these
lows here right
right here we lost one r on the
new york open because we thought that
trend was going to continue down after
kind of coming back to this range
so for that day we only made 1.4 r
the third trade we locked in really
nicely
um on the new york session again we were
looking for
bias uh to be to the downside here again
we can kind of pull up some clips here
um of of the bias analysis of that day
there
for our gonna be closing an
hour and a half so it is possible it
comes back up here but it did re-test
that order block looking bearish on that
side
one hour very bearish or block
rejection sweep very bearish
so coming into the five minute
we'd expect some sort of sweeping action
over this
into the some sort of move up into this
and our targets again these lows um and
uh we dropped off super super hard
i actually remember laughing so so hard
at this because i thought it was going
to get sopped out and it just dropped
super quick
so we got i think uh 3.8 r on that
locked in really really quickly
um and then the fourth trade here uh
continuing i think this was
on the same day uh we continued that
trend later into the day
just following that short bias really
really strong short bias for the week so
it's quite
easy for us to actually lock in profit
not every week is like this honestly
guys uh the current week that we're
trading
in on uh it's basically just ranging so
it's quite difficult to trade
it's already get out of here so that uh
that second day there we got six our
point two
profit uh third day here we got this one
almost right what ended up happening if
you look at the clip
uh in in the the recordings there um and
these these recordings are just for
uh the actual uh stream private uh
private members here on stream
right um and they can watch it later uh
so you guys can't actually see all of
those
but what actually did end up happening
here is we had triple top here
and it would have actually gone to these
lows here we would have actually taken
some profit
but i instead i took these the smart
action
and i closed it out just a small loss
there and then the trade six
right after that um we took a long after
a very explosive move
we were talking about this on stream i
remember saying this uh that we wanted
it to come back down but not
too deep right after a very strong move
like that
we want it to come down maybe about 50
and then we can continue that trend
uh just because if it comes down super
super deep then that's gonna be kind of
a fake out and then we're not gonna be
so so
confident in that move anymore and we
continued that and we were able to lock
in some profits that way
here might be the long a
if we got see we got that sweep
structure build right around that area
that we wanted it to
lines up well if we want it if we want
to if we want to enter on that breakout
then i'll be happy with that one so
stops
these low 1.21378
entry was 1.21496 our final target is
going to be
3r at 8.50 so in the total week we got
um
we got a total of 9.6 r locked in with
those scalp trades there right guys so
this video is called something like uh
how to predict the market perfectly
something like that
um i'm going to show you quickly at the
end here how i'm able to actually
predict
the market directions perfectly so um
jumping into
how do we actually predict the market
movements in perfect uh unison
uh and perfect accuracy right um
basically what i'm doing is i'm just
using the higher time frame here guys
and and we're just looking for you know
these really really high ones the daily
weekly monthly
uh these ones we're basically just
looking at like in a single candle
closes like when we saw
something like this when we saw that
sweep we knew that
the market was going to be coming down
during that day right uh when we when we
scroll back down here right
we knew that that was going to be coming
back down that next day so we were
looking for shorts during that day right
um and that was the weekly like the
daily here right
we could say okay you know there's maybe
a sweep like that on the daily really
really bullish uh close on the daily
there right
really bearish close on the daily here
so most likely we're going to be looking
for those similar
levels we're also going to be looking at
things like you know
breakers that can be rejected off of
right so this can
be a rejection on the higher time frame
we're going to be looking at
inefficiencies things like this and
these are all things that you guys are
going to need to know
and so just general moving points right
you're going to see at least a small
reaction off of each of these points on
the higher time frame
as we get down to the lower time frames
uh four hour and one hour
we're just basically looking at the
trend here right and the trend is kind
of your friend until it ends right
you guys heard this stuff before right
um so you're just kind of following the
trend until you find those higher time
frame zones
and it's as simple as that and then all
you got to do to actually get the actual
trades right at that point is find some
sort of entry mechanism guys
leave it at that 100 see you guys next
[Music]
time
oh